就是这儿
This is it.
如果完成这条绝佳的路线 我们会被载入史册
This fine trail, we're gonna be the first ever to complete it.
你疯了吧 犹他
You're insane, Utah.
-无路可行了 -有路啊
- There's no way to ride that. - There's a way.
相信我
You just gotta trust.
来吧 杰夫 赞助商就希望看到这样的画面
Come on, Jeff. This is exactly what our sponsors want.
把不可能变成可能 YouTube点击量一定会疯狂上升
The impossible realized. And all those YouTube hits.
无论如何 我们得赢得身下的坐骑
Anyway, we gotta earn these bikes we're sittin' on,
总好过为谋生而工作
and it beats workin' for a livin'.
好吧 如果让我为谋生而工作的话
Yeah, well... While I'm workin' for a livin',
小心你下半辈子
you'll be suckin' meals
都瘫痪在床上吃流食
through a straw for the rest of your life.
没事 我爱吃冰沙
I like smoothies.
我们就要成功了 兄弟
We got this, bro'.
跟我走
Just follow my line.
犹他呼叫直升机 我们要开始了
Utah to Heli, we're doin' this.
来啊 伙计
Come on, man!
杰夫 杰夫
Jeff! Jeff!
-坚持住 坚持 -把油门开到底
- Hold on, hold on! - Gas to that gas tank!
拉 使劲拉
Pull! Come on, pull!
极盗者
七年后
这是一个崭新的世界 孩子
This is a new world, son.
从加入联邦调查局那一刻起 你便身处前线
When you join the FBI, you join the front line
在秩序和混乱之间作战
in the war between order and chaos.
那么 问题来了 你准备好战斗了吗 犹他
So, the question is, are you ready for that fight, Utah?
布里格姆 长官
Brigham, sir.
我叫布里格姆
My name's Brigham.
犹他是我同学在YouTube上给我起的外号
Utah's a nickname my classmates got off YouTube.
你曾经生活的环境
That world that you came out of...
充满野性 嗯哼
Pretty wild, huh?
有时是
It had its moments.
为什么要舍弃那一切
Why leave all that
就为了进入组织
for all this structure?
或许是因为我可以利用这个组织 长官
Maybe I could use some structure, sir.
或许你
And maybe there's a part of
并不想与之有任何关联
you doesn't want anything to do with it. Hmm?
我知道你为什么离开你的圈子
I know why you left that world.
我知道那个孩子发生了什么
I know what happened in that world to that kid.
我是说杰夫 对吧
Jeff, was it?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
你有多么想要这个职位
How bad do you really want this?
我宁愿23岁才拿到高中学历 长官
Bad enough to have gotten my high school equivalency at 23, sir.
我宁愿同龄人都毕业五年后
Bad enough to have gone to college and law school
我才踏入大学和法学院
five years after my peers had graduated.
嗯 我看到了
Yeah, I saw that.
被录取进这个项目之前
The Bureau reviewed all my
办事处检查了我所有的证件
credentials before they admitted me into this program.
我不知道你为什么要再次审查
I'm not sure why you're second-guessing them.
因为这是我的工作 孩子
Because it's my job, son,
只让最有资格的人过我这一关
to only let the most qualified get past me.
因为我不确信你是否真的是一名合格的
Because I'm not convinced that you are an FBI agent
联邦调查局探员
in the making.
-我想要这个职位 -好吧 那让我看看你的本事
- I want this. - Well, then, show me.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
这是一场混战
This is what chaos looks like.
精密安排 毫无差错
And make no mistake,
这些罪犯非常 非常聪明
these perps were very, very smart.
也很幽默
Had a sense of humor, too.
任务完成
一千万克拉钻石被盗
10 million carats of diamonds were lost.
马哈娜卡梦
And Mahana Carbon
是一所主要由美国控股的公司
is a majority American-owned company,
所以与我们联邦调查局 利害相关
so we, the FBI, are interested.
上个月的30号是星期五
30th of last month was a Friday,
公司整个月的矿藏
so, the entire month's
都在那天出产
yield from the company's mines was on hand.
他们错就错在 不相信有人会来抢劫
Their mistake was believing that nobody could ever rob
不相信有人能从一百层楼的高度
and successfully make a getaway from a sorting facility
成功逃脱
100 stories above the Earth.
保安丝毫没料到
And their security failed to foresee
会有这样一群技艺非凡的罪犯
that there might exist a set of perps with an unusual skill set.
当他们看到地面警察干预出现时
They saw potential police intervention on the ground,
随之即兴表演了一番
and they improvised.
然后带着一千万克拉 原生未切割的钻石逃之夭夭
They got away with 100 million in uncut diamonds,
全部分发给孟买平民窟里
and then gave it all away to the poorest of the poor
最贫穷的人们
in the slums of Mumbai.
究竟是谁会做这种事
Who in the world would do that?
这个案子迫在眉睫 这些家伙此刻就在外兴风作案
This case is right now. These guys are out there in real time.
我需要一个推断
And I need a theory.
我们现在要对付的到底是什么样的人
What kind of people are we dealing with here?
活动坡道超控故障
Malfunction to ramp override.
妈的
Oh, shit!
先生 请问发生了什么
Sir, what's going on?
一辆运输现金的美国飞机遭到劫持
U.S. Plane carrying money
在墨西哥圣路易斯波托西上空
got hijacked over San Luis Potosi in Mexico.
罪犯们跳进从林 消失得无影无踪
Perps jumped out over the jungle and disappeared without a trace.
我们正在搜寻尸体
We're looking for the bodies.
打扰了 长官
Excuse me, sir.
您有空吗
Do you have a minute?
两起案件发生在两个不同的大洲上
We have two crimes on two different continents.
孟买的钻石失窃
Diamond-sorting facility in Mumbai,
和今天墨西哥的飞机抢劫
and today's cargo plane over Mexico.
但是 还有第三起案件 发生在第三个大洲上
But there's a third crime on a third continent.
大约一个月前
Remember about a month ago,
有一家
there was an international
木材建筑群烧为平地
logging complex that was burned to the ground
-正是在刚果河沿岸 -嗯
- on the banks of the Congo River... - Yeah.
刚果河是世界上最危险的急流
Which is where the world's most dangerous rapids are.
据我目前推断
Now I think the people that started that fire
制造那起火灾的人
also became the first
也是史上首位横渡印加激流并存活的人
ever to navigate and survive the Inga Rapids.
你的意思是这和那两件有关吗
You're saying this is connected to the other two?
我认为他们息息相关 长官
I think they're all connected, sir.
看这
Here.
孟买失窃两天前
Two days before the Mumbai heist,
仅一千公里以外
only 1,000 miles away, these three were photographed
有人拍到这三个人从珠穆朗玛峰顶跃下的照片
base-jumping from the peak of Everest.
他们都是同一拨人
They're the same people.
同一拨人
Same people...
他们这么做到底是为了什么
Then what are they really up to here?
我不知道他们为什么要犯罪 长官
I don't know why they're committing the crimes, sir.
但是我想到了他们在追求什么
But I have an idea what they're chasing.
我认为他们想完成尾崎八项
I think they're attempting something called The Ozaki Eight.
这个人是小野尾崎
This is Ono Ozaki.
一名环保卫士
He was an eco-warrior,
首批公众认可的多项极限运动员之一
one of the first recognized Extreme Poly-Athletes.
他挑战八项考验的世界极限运动
Now he challenged the Extreme Sports world to a series
他说这是尊重自然的力量
of eight ordeals that he said honored the forces of nature.
他相信 寻找完美路线
Anyone who could find the perfect line existing
完成每一项考验的人
through each one of these ordeals,
就能得到涅槃
he believed, would achieve nirvana.
照你这么说 这与金钱无关
So, this is not about money?
而是精神启迪吗
It's about spiritual enlightenment?
正是如此
Exactly.
一名极限运动员有可能终身训练
An extreme athlete could potentially train
就为了完成这些考验中的一项
their entire life just to attempt one of these ordeals.
实现所有八项 几乎是不可能完成的任务
To complete all eight, would be to complete the impossible.
史上从未有人成功过
No one's ever done it.
尾崎他本人在完成第三项时身亡
Ozaki himself died attempting his third ordeal.
这些家伙们已经完成了前三项
These guys have already completed the first three.
力之涌动 在非洲完成
"Emerging Force" In Africa.
天之降诞 在珠峰实现
"Birth of Sky" On Everest.
以及刚刚发生在墨西哥的地之觉醒
And "Awakening Earth" In Mexico.
第四项是什么
What's number four?
水之生灵
It's called "Life of Water."
国家气象中心
The National Weather Service
目前正在追踪大西洋低气压云团
is tracking a low-pressure system in the Atlantic.
一场将要袭击法国西海岸的巨大风暴
A massive storm about to hit off the coast of western France.
风暴结束时 会出现惊世涌浪
And when it clears, it's gonna cause a giant swell.
这种浪潮十年一现
We're talkin' once-in-a-decade waves.
超过八十英尺高
Eighty feet-plus.
长官 如果我的推断无误 他们将去往那里
Sir, if I'm right, that's where they'll be.
你有正装吗 孩子
You own a suit, son?
在我决心去联邦调查局之前
Before finding my way to the FBI,
我曾是一名多项极限运动员
I was what's called an Extreme Sports Poly-Athlete.
单板滑雪 摩托车越野
Snowboarding, motocross,
几乎所有高山速降项目
any downhill mountain sport, really.
还有一些登高运动
And a few up.
霍尔
Hall!
半小时之内我得飞往墨西哥
I'm supposed to be on a plane to Mexico in half an hour.
你叫我听这个有何用意
Why am I listening to this?
就五分钟
Five minutes.
我确信 那些墨西哥和孟买的罪犯们
I believe the people behind the robberies in Mexico
都是极限运动员
as well as the one in Mumbai are extreme athletes.
这不是明摆着的吗
Isn't that obvious?
我觉得如果不是极限运动员
I don't think you ride a motorcycle off a building,
不太可能有能力骑摩托车跃下建筑物或者跳下货运飞机
or skydive out of a cargo plane if you aren't.
最后一对罪犯在雨林中留下了降落的坑记
That last pair cratered somewhere in the jungle.
我认为他们没有进入丛林
I don't think they went into the jungle at all.
而是直接穿了过去
I think they went through it.
墨西哥燕子洞
Cave of the Swallows.
地球上最大的自然矿洞
This is the largest natural cave shaft on Earth.
理论上能容纳一座帝国大厦
The Empire State Building could literally fit inside it.
正好与圣路易斯波托西相邻
And it just happens to be located adjacent to San Luis Potosi.
那些罪犯心知肚明
The perps knew that.
他们设计了精密的路线
They surgically identified the perfect line
确保万无一失穿过丛林
that would intersect them with the jungle
并准确到达目的地
exactly where they wanted.
这样一来 他们就成为了史上首次且唯一
In doing so, they became the first and only
进入燕子洞完成地空转换的人
to make a sky-earth transition into the Cave of Swallows.
可是 罪犯的动机是什么
But what is the motive for the crimes?
这与那些骑着摩托车窃取钻石的家伙
And what does this have to do with guys driving motorcycles
又有什么关系
out of diamond-sorting facilities?
还有那些在墨西哥中部下钞票雨的人
Or raining U.S. Currency down over central Mexico?
嗯 长官 这正是我们需要探究的
Well, sir, that's what we need to find out.
那些官员
Those people in there,
他们不同意你的推断
they didn't buy your theory.
但我相信你
But I did.
这是个临时身份证
This is a provisional I.D.
你得赶去法国
You're on your way to France.
特务帕帕斯会在英国办事处外与你会面
You'll be met there by Agent Pappas out of the U.K. Office.
他一开始
Now, he's...
不太好接触 但你可以信任他
an acquired taste, but you can trust him.
一切听他安排 明白吗
I want you to do exactly as he says, you understand?
是 长官
Yes, sir.
你的工作就是查明这些人的身份
Your job, identify these individuals,
探明罪犯
find out what the connection
与那些考验之间的联系
is between the crimes and the ordeals.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
别让我失望 要是搞砸了我也会受牵连
Don't let me down, 'cause my ass is on the line in this.
不会的 您放心
I don't plan on it, sir.
比亚里茨 法国
你是说冲浪吗 在大海中央
Surfing? In the middle of the ocean?
是 风暴会引起巨浪
Yeah, the storm causes a swell.
在深海处前进几千公里
It travels thousands of miles through deep water,
突然到达一座海底山峰处 然后就
then suddenly reaches an underwater mountain, and it...
别废话 该出发了
Load your shit. It's time to roll.
你说的这些 况且称其为假设
So, by your, for lack of a better word, "Hypothesis,"
如果这些家伙真的存在 他们会来这儿吗
if these guys exist, they'd be out here?
他们没有理由缺席这么精彩的浪潮
Freak spring swell like this, there's no way they'd miss it.
没人知道下一次会是什么时候
No one knows when the next one's gonna hit.
可能是一年内的科尔特斯海岸 或许五年十年
It could be Cortes Bank in a year, or maybe five, maybe 10.
再想寻找这样的机会无疑是大海捞针
It's a needle in a haystack after this.
恭喜 你捞到针了
Congrats. You found your haystack.
再来一次
Pick up, pick up!
你以前这样冲过浪吗
You ever surf anything like this?
我冲过浪
I've surfed.
嗯 但是你冲过这么高的浪吗
Yeah, but you ever surfed anything like this?
准备好了吗 走
Are you ready? Let's go!
来玩一天吧
Here comes the set of the day!
该死
Oh, shit.
看 有两个人去抢同一个浪
Look! There's two guys going for the same wave!
谁会进去呢
Who's got the inside?
-怎么了 伙计 -回去 兄弟 这不是你的浪
- What the hell, man? - Back, man! It's not your wave!
他们懂了
They got it!
那个家伙在抢浪
That guy, he's snaking the wave!
你这样会伤害到别人的 伙计
You're gonna get somebody killed, man!
发生什么了
What's going on?
巴黎旧火车站 明晚
The old train station in Paris, tomorrow night.
这次你要加入吗
You gonna jump in this time?
上次的事我还耿耿于怀
I'm still hurting from the last one.
-你是那个被我抢浪的人 对吗 -是的
- You're the guy I snaked, right? - Yup.
也是把你从大海深处捞上来的人
And the one who plucked you off the ocean floor.
我猜你以前没有冲过这么大的浪 对吗
I guess you never surfed anything that big before, right?
-有人冲过吗 -他差点就做到了
- Has anybody? - He almost did.
差点
Almost.
很抱歉
Sorry.
不是你的错 是我自己做的决定
You didn't make the choice for me. I did.
他还活着吗 真可惜
So, he's alive? Shame.
客气一点 罗奇 你不知道我们的客人是何方神圣吗
Easy, Roach. Don't you know who our guest is?
是谁
Who is it?
约翰尼·犹他
Johnny Utah.
罗奇·卢汀格 对吗
"Roach" Rottinger, right?
你是摩托界的传奇 伙计
You're a moto legend, man.
来吧 放轻松
Come on, chill out.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
一名越野摩托车手在今天那样的巨浪上干什么
What's a motocross rider doing on a wave like that?
你今天差点粉身碎骨 兄弟
You almost got your own ass killed today, brother.
玩的就是刺激 不是吗
Sort of the point, isn't it?
嗨 伙计 这是你的船吗
Hey, man, is this your boat?
我只有一口锅 别想往里面小便
The only pot I have, you can't even piss in.
这艘船是他的
The boat is his.
阿尔·佛里克 他赞助我们
Al Fariq. He sponsors us.
赞助你们干什么
Sponsors you to what?
成为第一个实现不可能的人
To be the first to achieve the impossible.
-嗨 伙计 -差点就得手了 兄弟
- Hey, man. - Almost had it, brother.
差点
Almost.
-下次 -下次吧
- Next time. - Next time.
-我会成功的 对吗 -当然
- It'll come to me. Right? - Yeah.
大家在这玩的开心吗
Are you enjoying my party?
嗨 他和我们是一伙的
Hey, that's our guy.
-玩的开心吗 -当然 老兄
Having fun? MAN: Yeah, man.
很好 你呢
Good. You, too?
嗨 我以前怎么不认识你
Hey, how come I don't know you?
世界之大 你为什么一定认识我
Big world. Why would you?
像你这样的巨浪选手 我常翻YouTube
Big wave rider like you? I watch YouTube.
只是从来没见过你
I just never seen you.
森林中有棵树倒下 没人把它录下来放上YouTube
A tree falls in the forest, no one puts it on YouTube,
但这件事没有发生吗
did it ever really happen?
说得对
Right.
他们叫我博迪
They call me Bodhi.
对一个陌生人你问的太多了
You're asking a lot of questions for someone you don't know.
我们俩还有事情要做 好吗
You and I got something to do. Okay?
乔达会带你转转
Chowder will show you around.
不 我不
No, I won't.
那你自己玩吧 好好享受
You're on your own. Enjoy the party.
大家都玩得开心啊
Everyone have a good time!
-玩的开心吗 -最糟糕的聚会
- Having fun? - Worst party ever!
最糟糕的聚会？那下次你别来了
Worst party ever? You're never gonna get invited again.
-十分感谢 -好啊
Thank you very much. BODHl: Okay.
这儿真好
It's nice up here.
珊莎拉
Samsara.
约翰尼
Johnny.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
我今天看到你冲浪的样子 令人敬佩
I saw you on that wave today. It was epic.
我爱大海
I love the sea.
充满力量
Its power.
我今天确实体会到了
I got a real taste of that today.
-是啊 我看到你摔得狗吃屎 -噢 你看见了啊
- Yeah, I saw you eat shit. - Oh, you saw that?
很好
Good. Perfect.
-棒极了 -嗯哼
- That's awesome. - Hmm.
大自然总能让你感受到自己的渺小
Nature will always find a way to make you feel small.
博迪救了我 我欠他一命
I owe Bodhi for pullin' me out.
我们不相信亏欠
We don't believe in owing.
那你相信什么
What do you believe in?
你脚下的路是你自己决定的
That you choose your path.
你可是一名联邦调查局探员
You are an FBI agent.
好吧 只是暂时的
Well, provisional.
珊莎拉是什么意思
What does "Samsara" Mean?
流浪者
Wanderer.
流浪者也有目标吗
Can a wanderer have a path?
嗯 当然有
Yeah, for sure.
但只有当你停止追寻 你才能找到
But it's only when you stop looking for one that you find it.
我要如何停止追寻
How do I stop looking?
我们就待在这里吧
Let's just be here.
好啊
Okay.
-早上好 -嗨
- Morning. - Hey.
玩的开心吗
Had a good time?
聚会很棒 伙计
It's a good party, man.
你来这干什么 犹他
What are you doing here, Utah?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我记得你 名声远扬
I remember you. Your reputation.
勇多于谋
More balls than talent.
有人说或许那就是你杰出的原因
Some said maybe that was why you were so good.
因为你什么都不怕
'Cause you lacked fear.
但我昨天看到的
But what I saw on that wave yesterday,
却大不相同
that was different.
你缺乏尊重
You lacked respect.
没有亲戚
There was no... Connection.
也没有美人
There was no beauty.
或许我在追求什么 像你一样
Maybe I'm chasing something. Like you are.
像我吗
Like me?
你为什么认为我在追求什么
What do you think I'm chasing?
你在追求尾崎八项
You're chasing The Eight.
那是个传说
That's a myth.
真正的问题是
But the real question is,
你追求的是什么
what are you after?
昨夜真是太疯狂了
That was some crazy, crazy shit.
为此我要谢谢你
For that, I thank you.
肯定有什么不对 帕帕斯
There's gotta be something there, Pappas.
反正我只顾着喝酒
All I saw was the bottom of my glass.
和欣赏美女 你呢
And a great piece of ass. You?
我只知道
I just know there's gotta be a
那艘船上有很多家伙想要挑战八项
lotta guys on that boat who are chasing The Eight.
你掌握了对调查有力的相关证据吗
You got evidence that connects them to our investigation?
你什么都没拿到
You've got nothing.
我送你去飞机场
I'm takin' you to the airport.
-不 -你去登机吧
- No. - Putting you on a plane.
不是这样的 我昨晚在船上听到了谈话
No, I heard some talk on the boat last night
今晚巴黎会出事
about something going down in Paris tonight.
我会查清楚的
I gotta go check that out.
我挺喜欢你的 孩子
I like you, kid,
但如果你想继续调查此案
but if you wanna stay on the case,
你得给我看一些证据
you gotta give me some evidence.
我会的
You got it.
-打扰一下 火车站在哪 -什么
Excuse me. Train station? MAN: What?
谢谢
Thank you.
让他进来
Let him in.
他做傻事又不是一次两次了
It wouldn't be the first time he did something stupid.
世界真小
Small world.
他在这干什么
What's he doing here?
我让他在这里和我们会面
I told him to meet us here.
噢 是吗
Oh, you did?
嗯
Yeah.
他说他要找什么东西
He said he was after something.
在这儿你肯定能找到
No better place to find it.
好吧
Okay, then.
欢迎
Welcome.
我只是来看看 伙计
I just came to catch the scene, man.
你看到了
You're catchin' it.
让他过来
Let go.
你就这点本事
There you are.
我知道我在找什么了
I think I know what I'm after.
你知道个屁
You don't know shit.
我今晚出去找一座山
I'm headed out tonight to find us a mountain,
很有希望抵达路线
and hopefully arrive at the line.
你觉得要多久
How long you think it'll take?
可能一周
Maybe a week.
祝你好运 兄弟
Good luck, brother.
等我一下
Give me a minute.
很有品味
It's pretty decent.
有些东西我不会将就
There are a few things in life I don't compromise on.
不 在我印象里你很少将就
No, I don't get the impression you compromise on much ever.
尽量不将就
Try not to.
但世界太乱了
But the world's a pretty messed-up place,
我还是得生存下去
and I still gotta live in it.
那你隐居吗
So, you live off the grid?
不
No.
我们并不隐居
We live on it.
只是以我们自己的方式
Just on our own terms.
什么方式
What terms?
你不会懂的
You wouldn't get it.
我们改变世界 我们回馈
We change the grid. We give back.
自从那个孩子听从你的指引丧命悬崖 你就放弃寻找生命的真谛
The second that kid got killed on your line, you quit life.
你因为别人的选择改变主意
You turned away because of something someone else did.
你以前卖运动饮料
You were selling sports drinks?
好吧 我无权评说
Fine. That's not for me to judge.
但是你让其他人决定你生活的方向
But you let someone else determine the direction your life took.
我看不起你
That I judge.
你清楚一堆狗屁道理
So, you got all your shit figured out,
却不给勇敢尝试的人一个机会
and screw everyone else for trying, huh?
不是这样吗
Is that it?
尾崎的考验
Ozaki's ordeal.
风之永动
Life of Wind.
你想参加吗
You doing anything?
我们一无所获
We've got nothing.
他可能明早起飞
He'll probably be on a plane in the morning.
等一分钟
Hang on a minute.
该死
Shit!
我打入内部了
计划改变
Change of plans.
我猜博迪觉得你有前途
I guess Bodhi sees something in you.
但我不觉得
I don't.
我们黎明前往阿尔卑斯山脉
We leave for the Alps first light.
你一起来吗
You coming?
要徒步攀登多久
How long's the hike?
取决于你的速度 伙计
Depends how fast you are, man.
前方路还很长 我的朋友
We still have a long way to go, my friend.
那是峰顶
That's the summit.
半英里的原始岩石路
Half a mile of pure primordial rock.
或许我应该提前问问你的
Maybe I should have asked you this before,
但你之前有经验 对吗
but you've done this, right?
确实
Sure.
不过之前是从飞机上跳下来
Except it was out of a plane.
附近如果有飞机会阻碍我们前进
Proximity flight's a whole different monster.
你得读懂气流
You need to read the flow.
与风融为一体
Become the wind.
要不然你会达到一个点
Or you'll hit your point.
什么点
What point?
让你失去控制的点
The point where you break.
到那时你便成为恐惧的奴隶 被其主宰
Where fear becomes master, and you're its slave.
一个挑战极限的人
A man who pushes his boundaries
才能找到一切
ultimately finds them.
所以 你的意思是我会死的
So, basically, you're sayin' I'm gonna die.
我们都会死的
We're all gonna die.
只是怎么死
The only question's how.
那么
So,
你想接着走 还是转头回去
you wanna keep going, or are you turning around?
他来了
Here he is.
嗨 石头
Hey, the rock.
什么石头
What rock?
你听见他说的了 把石头给他
You heard the man. Pass the rock.
噢 你这混蛋
Oh, you funny assholes!
应该检查你的背包的 伙计
Should have checked your bag, man.
永远别忘记检查背包
Always check your bag.
啊哈 干得好
Ah! Great work.
-这个石头 -你还有一块吗
- This rock? - You have another one?
好吧
All right.
准备好了吗
Ready?
六秒钟
Six seconds.
六秒 要么飞要么死
Six seconds to fly or die.
我们什么时候走
When do we go?
黎明第一道曙光
First light.
好戏六天内就会上演
Happening in six days.
所以 我们要跳下山峰然后涅槃吗
So, we're gonna jump off a mountain and reach nirvana?
并不是那么简单
It's not that simple.
尾崎讲过平衡之道
Ozaki spoke of balance.
但这并不是为了私人利益而牺牲生命
But it's not about risking our lives for personal gain.
而是努力让自己
It is about becoming part of
成为更伟大的存在
something that is much greater than ourselves.
八项挑战是为了表达对地球自然之力的崇敬
The Eight honors the essential forces of the Earth.
尾崎想完成八项挑战
And Ozaki wanted to complete The Eight
让全世界重新关注这个星球的美好
to bring the world's attention back to the beauty of this planet.
然而地球已生命垂危
The fact that it is dying.
我们必须付出多于收获
We have to give more than we take
我们想阻止
if we want to stop the
这片生养我们的土地的毁灭
destruction of the very place that gives us life.
这就是我们的目的
That's the path we're on.
也是我们毕生的追寻
That's what we're looking for.
和信仰所在
That's what we're following.
我们来此并不是为了获得启迪 得到涅槃
We're not here to reach enlightenment, to find nirvana.
而是通过与之融为一体 来拯救这片土地
We're here to try to save this place by becoming one with it.
要做到这一点 你需要
And to do that, you need
放弃自我意识
to be able to let go of your sense of self.
完全放弃
Completely.
没有回头路
There's no turning back.
所以 朝着你心所指的方向前行吧 犹他
So, go whichever way your heart tells you, Utah.
如果你与我们是同路人
And if you are on the same path as we are,
那我们就黎明见吧
I may see you at dawn.
你准备好舍弃自我了吗
Are you ready to let go?
那就来吧
Let's do this.
你做到了
You did it!
是啊
Yeah!
恭喜你
Congratulations.
谢谢 伙计
Thanks, man.
耶
Yeah!
干得漂亮
That's how you do it.
耶 耶
Yeah! Yeah!
-你们准备好了吗 -噢 当然
- You guys ready? - Oh, yeah.
-来吧 -让我看看
- Here you go. - Let me see.
-有点儿干 -味道不错
- It's a little dry. - Tastes good.
-好了吗 -好了
- All right? - Yeah.
来吧
Ready?
欢迎 约翰尼
Welcome, Johnny.
谢谢你
Thank you.
吃饭吧
Let's eat.
-好的 -好
- Yeah. - Okay.
我妈妈是犹特印第安人
My mom was a Ute Indian.
所以大家都管我叫犹他
That's why they call me Utah.
意思是 山里的人
Means "Mountain people."
也许正因如此我才对斜坡运动如此在行
Maybe that's why I was so good on the slopes.
杰夫就像我的亲兄弟 不止是朋友
Jeff was like a brother to me. More than a friend.
可他因我而死
And he died because of me.
那是一场悲剧
What happened to your friend was tragic.
但却是他自己的选择 与你无关
But it was his choice, not yours.
我们只能为自己的选择负责 兄弟
We can only be responsible for our own path, brother.
而无须干涉他人
And let others have theirs.
冰之固结 第六场考验
"Life of Ice." The Sixth Ordeal.
乔达在意大利发现了那片山脉 但没找到合适的路线
Chowder found the mountain in Italy, but not the line.
必须找到一条线路 而且得快点找到
You gotta find a line, you gotta do it fast.
暴风雪就快来了
Weather's rolling in.
我们可不能被它困在这儿
You don't wanna get caught up here when it does.
都不知道这块岩石能不能滑
If this rock's even rideable.
那边那一块如何呢
What about that one over there?
肯定很好滑
Definitely first descent.
-不行 -不行吗
- No. - No?
你觉得不够刺激吗
Not radical enough for you?
足够刺激了
It's radical enough.
那为什么不行
Then what's wrong with it?
这样不够帅
It's not beautiful.
这关乎生死 一点也不帅
That's not beautiful. That's death.
也许吧 但这样的挑战也很完美
Maybe. But it's also perfect.
我去
Shit...
噢
Oh!
-行动起来吧 -好的
- Let's do this. - Right.
我来照应你们 我会看着直升机的
I got you. I'll be with the chopper.
没路了 到此为止吧 我们被悬崖截住了
That's it. We're done. We're cliffed out.
格罗美特 把直升机调过来 结束了
Grommet? Send the chopper. It's over.
-收到 -不管了
- Copy that. - Screw that.
这家伙真是疯了
This guy is seriously broke.
挺伟大的 不是吗
Kind of great, isn't it?
如果我们死在这儿了
We're never gonna finish
剩下的事可就没法完成了
what we started if we die on this mountain.
我们必须这样做
We have to do this.
罗奇
Roach...
乔达死了
We lost Chowder.
噢 天啊
Oh, man.
他就在那上面 我们得找到他
He's up there! We gotta find him!
他死了 你帮不上忙的 跟你没关系
He's dead! You can't help it! It's not about you!
-你疯了吗 那是我的路线 -你的路线
- Are you crazy? That was my line! - Your line?
一旦他下定了决心 那就是他的路线了
The second he committed to it, it became his line!
不是你的
Not yours.
别想了
Let it go.
回头见 兄弟
See you soon, brother.
回见
See you soon.
-敬乔达 大伙儿 -敬乔达
- Here's to Chowder, guys! - To Chowder!
不是吧 犹他来了
Shit! It's Utah!
-犹他 犹他 伙计 -你好吗 伙计
- Utah! Utah, man! - What's up, man?
你去哪里了啊
Where did you come from?
我在火星上待了一阵 在火星上
I've been on Mars, man. I've been on Mars.
-回见 -嘿 兄弟
- Peace, peace. - Hey, bro.
瞧瞧我的兄弟们在孟买干了什么
Man, check out what my boys were doing in Mumbai.
见到你很高兴
Good to see you, man.
在孟买 那三个降落伞 伙计
In Mumbai? The three parachutes? Dude.
-我知道 我知道 我得走了 -别走啊
- I know, I know. I gotta go... - Don't go!
我很快就回来 我会回来的 稍等 就一会儿
I'll be back in one minute. I'll be back, just wait. One minute!
嘿 犹他
Hey, Utah!
嘿 很荣幸你能来这儿
Hey, it's my pleasure to have you here.
我这里永远都欢迎你
You are always welcome chez Al Fariq.
我喜欢你 约翰尼
I like you, Johnny.
你希望你加入我的队伍
I want you on my team, man!
超胆侠梦想成真了
Daredevil dreams come true.
我可以让你成为英雄
I can make you a hero,
或看着你在不断尝试中死去 呃
or I can watch you die trying. Eh?
看看那个混球
Look at that asshole.
他比大多数小国家还有钱
He's got more money than most small nations.
嘿 史蒂夫
Hey, Steve!
你还好吗
You all right?
他会抬腿撒尿
Lifted up his leg and pissed
把这种暴行施加于整座山脉
out this atrocity all over the mountains.
呼
Whoo!
你知道吗 这些山并不归他所有
You know, he doesn't own these mountains,
就像我们也不归他所有一样
just like he doesn't own us.
蛋糕 蛋糕 蛋糕 来吧
Cake, cake, cake! Come on!
你好吗
You good?
嗯
Yeah.
在启迪之路上我们掠夺了很多东西
Man, I see a lot of taking on the way to enlightenment.
难道不应该回报吗
What's being given back?
相信我
Trust me.
我们懂得回报
We give back.
你想单独待着吗
Do you need privacy?
不 不用
No. I'm good.
所有人都走了吗
Everybody leave?
嗯 基本上都走了
Yeah, mostly.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
想着乔达的死
Thinkin' about losing Chowder.
如果这个派对的任何一部分与尾崎心目中的
If any of this party is what Ozaki had in mind
启迪之路有关的话
for the path to enlightenment.
他会恨死这一切的
Ozaki would have hated this.
他只在乎“八次考验”的纯粹性
He only cared about the purity of The Eight
以及在接受这些考验时
and giving back whatever he took from the Earth
回报从地球索取的一切
on the way to getting there.
那他都回报了些什么呢
And what did he give back?
有时候很简单 比如种种树
Sometimes it was as simple as planting a tree.
有时候 是一些更加困难的事
Other times, it was something much larger.
比如说 在我九岁那年 我父母在一次雪崩中丧生后
Like when my parents died in an avalanche when I was nine,
他给了我一个家
he gave me a home.
我不知道这件事
I didn't know.
抱歉
Sorry.
我只知道他在探索第三次考验时丧生了
I know that he died questing his third ordeal.
是啊 事情是这样发展的
Yeah. That's the story.
但不是全部真相
But it's not the truth.
他完成了那次考验
He completed that ordeal.
他本可以完成全部八次考验的
He could have finished the entire Eight.
他就是那么的厉害
He was that good.
但是他却因为那次考验之后的回报而遇害了
But instead he got himself killed giving back for that ordeal.
怎么遇害的
How?
在北大西洋 他驾着小船驶到了
He positioned his small boat in the North Atlantic
一艘挪威捕鲸船和一群座头鲸之间
between a Norwegian whaling ship and a pod of humpback whales.
那艘捕鲸船甚至没有减速
The whaling ship never even slowed.
唯一的幸存者是一个跟他一起在船上的年轻人
The only survivor was a young guy who was on the boat with him.
嗯 那个年轻人为什么没有说出真相呢
Well, why didn't this young guy say something?
他为什么不说出来
Why didn't he tell the world?
也许他有其他想法吧
Maybe he had other ideas.
反正也没什么意义了
It wouldn't have made a difference anyway.
尽管我十分崇拜尾崎
As much as I worshipped Ozaki,
但那就是他唯一的致命伤
that was his Achilles' heel.
他真诚地相信着能通过自己的观点来改变世界
He truly believed that he could change the world with an idea.
观念可以产生伟大的力量
Ideas can be powerful.
可却比不上一艘捕鲸船的威力
Not as powerful as a whaling ship.
如果观念不够强大的话 那还剩什么呢
If not ideas, then what else is there?
行动
Action.
船上的那个年轻人
That young guy on the boat.
是博迪 对吗
That was Bodhi, wasn't it?
博迪打算完成尾崎未竟的事业
Bodhi is going to complete what Ozaki set out to do.
他将换一种方式来完成它
He's going to take a different path to do it.
所以 他召集了我们
So, here we are.
我尽可能快地赶过来了
Came as fast as I could.
是啊 都过了十二天了
Yeah. It's been 12 days.
我抓住了一个机会 我不能暴露身份
I saw an opportunity. I couldn't break cover.
我在阿尔·佛里克的藏身之处安装了二十四小时监控
I put a 24-hour surveillance on Al Fariq's hideaway.
你的一举一动我都了如指掌
I know exactly what you were doing.
犯罪智多星
Criminal masterminds?
他们只是一群受阿尔·佛里克金钱支配
They're just kids partying away their lives
浪费生命的孩子罢了
on Al Fariq's dime.
他们与你的区别就是
The difference between them and you,
你是在联邦调查局的指挥下做事的
is you're doing it on the FBI's.
帕帕斯
Pappas...
那你又干了些什么呢 哈
Where does that leave you, huh?
在我进行调查时就在这个码头闲逛吗
Hangin' out on this dock while I'm onto something?
你什么也没调查出来
You're onto shit!
我很抱歉 这次行动
Now I'm sorry if this particular
不像你喜欢的那样充满诱惑力
locale lacks the glamour you're accustomed to
这儿没有毒品
because there's no drugs,
也没有裸着身体扭屁股的小姑娘
or naked girls shakin' their arses.
但这就是我们整夜守在这儿的原因
But that's why we stayed down 'ere all night.
即证明这一切麻烦事
To prove that wasn't an
并非因一个美国矿井而起
American mine that blew that piece of shit up!
顺便告诉你 这就是联邦调查局的日常工作
For your information, this is how the real FBI works.
既肮脏又平淡 并且通常极其无聊
It's dirty, it's pedestrian, and generally downright boring!
我可以弄清楚这一切的 帕帕斯
I can figure this out, Pappas!
我只是需要更多时间
I just need more time.
你离开一天了
You've been gone a day.
你他妈去哪儿了
Where the fuck have you been?
准备好去回报了吗
Ready to start talkin' about giving back?
她给予
She gives.
我们享用
We partake.
然后我们回报她
And then we give her an offering.
回报什么
An offering of what?
底下那个矿井
That mine down there
已经被人连续二十多年从她的心脏掠取黄金
has been ripping gold out of her guts for over 20 years.
我们要归还一部分回去
We're gonna get some of it back for her.
尘归尘 土归土
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust, my man.
物归原主
Source to source.
你打算去偷窃
You're gonna steal it?
不
No.
我们打算解放它
We're going to liberate it.
什么时候下去
When's this goin' down?
就现在 兄弟
Right now, brother.
我知道了 好吗 有人在四处作乱
I get it, okay? People are screwing up the world.
你想阻止想挽回
And you wanna do something about it,
但你得换种方式
then you gotta find another way!
整个世界都在燃烧 你看看周围
The world is burning! Look around!
-你有更好的主意吗 -大概还有一百种办法
- Do you have a better idea? - There's about a hundred ways
这可能会惹出大乱子
this could go really wrong, man.
那种规模的爆炸
Explosives like that...
一旦越过了这条线 你就无法回头了
You're gonna cross a line you can't come back from.
这就是我俩的区别所在
That's the difference between us.
你眼里只有界限
All you see is lines.
我们眼里却是真相
We see the truth.
把那个戴上
Put that on.
待在我后面
Stay behind me!
不 不
No, no!
快走吧 快出去
Get outta here! Get out!
走 走 快跑
Leave! Leave! Run!
快离开
Get outta here!
离开卡车 跑 快跑
Leave the truck! Run! Run!
快点 约翰尼
Come on, Johnny!
一切就绪
All set.
出来 快出来 快从那里出来
Get out! Get out! Get out of there!
出来
Get out!
帮帮我 帮我一把 帮帮我
Help me! Gimme a hand! Help me!
把他放下
Put him down here.
博迪 别动 联邦调查局
Bodhi, Freeze, FBI!
我不能让你这么做 兄弟
I can't let you do it, brother!
见鬼 博迪 把它放下
Damn it, Bodhi, drop that!
好了 我们得离开这儿 走吧
That's it. We gotta get outta here! Let's go!
原来是你
It was you the whole time!
孟买 非洲 墨西哥 所有的一切
Mumbai, Africa, Mexico. Everything!
如果你真的想知道的话 你只需开口问我
If you really wanted to know, all you had to do was ask.
第一次在巴黎见你时
When you showed up in Paris,
我们就知道你是警察了
we knew you were a cop.
那你为什么让我加入
Then why'd you let me in?
因为我相信自己可以拯救你
Because I thought I could save you.
那时我的摩托车失去了控制
That's when I lost control of the motorcycle
撞入了河里
and crashed into the river.
等我浮出水面 返回河岸时
By the time I got back to the surface and the riverbank,
他已经离开了
he was gone.
你的任务是调查并上报
Your orders were to investigate and report.
所以 现在我又有了新的状况
So, now I got another situation.
格劳曼矿场损失了价值一亿美元的黄金矿石
$100 million in gold ore lost from Grauman Minerals,
你也知道 这又是一起
which as you know, is another multi-national
与美国脱不开干系的跨国大案
with American ties.
我的主管火急火燎
And I got the Director on
把我从华盛顿派过来了结此事
my ass sending me here from D.C. To end this.
所以 我的疑问是
So, my question...
你为什么没有服从指令 孩子
Why did you not follow your instructions, son?
我赢得了他们的信任 长官 并且我想
I'd earned their trust, sir, and I wanted to be sure
弄清他们是否真的是嫌疑犯
they were the suspects.
所以 你的计划就是帮助他们再次犯罪吗
So, your M.O. Is to help them commit another crime?
不 不是这样的 我是想阻止他们
No! Not at all. I wanted to stop them.
-是吗 -我试着去阻止他们
- Yeah... - I tried to stop them.
博迪并不认为这是在犯罪
Bodhi doesn't see these as crimes.
他把这视作给予
He thinks of them as offerings.
给予 这是什么意思
Offerings? What the hell does that mean?
这究竟是什么意思
What the hell does that even mean?
这些人想完成尾崎的八次考验
These guys are trying to complete the Ozaki Eight.
他们把这视作地球对他们的恩赐
They see that as a gift given to them from the Earth.
为了回报恩赐 他们就想把某些从地球索取的东西
To balance out that gift, they want to give back
还回去
something taken from the Earth.
在这起案子里 被索取的就是黄金矿石
This case, it was gold ore that was ripped out of the ground.
那么你做卧底多久 两周吗
Now you've been undercover, what, two weeks?
你知道失去洞察力是多么的容易吗 孩子
You know how easy it is to lose perspective, son?
事情的关键是 你离这些罪犯太近了
What happened here, you got too close to these individuals.
你偏偏做了我让你千万不要做的那些事
You did exactly what I told you not to do!
我想抓住这群人 长官 就同你一样
I wanna catch these guys, sir. Just like you.
但他们不是普通的罪犯
But they're not common criminals.
他们并不是那样看待自己的
They just don't see themselves that way.
他们把尾崎的理念发挥到了极限
They've taken Ozaki's ideas to the extreme.
他们觉得自己是从事高尚事业的十字军战士
They think they're crusaders with a worthy cause.
他们完全可以为此献出生命
They're more than willing to die for it.
每个罪犯都能为自己的罪行编造出正当理由
Every criminal has some bullshit justification for what they do.
也正像其他罪犯一样
And just like every other identified criminal,
他们的资料都在国际刑警这里了
their profiles are here at Interpol.
一旦他们有所行动 我们就能将其抓捕归案
They will make a move, and we will catch them.
我们冻结了阿尔·佛里克的资产
We've frozen Al Fariq's assets.
他们的钱都没了
Their money is gone.
这些人谨小慎微
These guys are meticulous.
一举一动都几乎毫无破绽
Everything they do is near flawless.
但如果我们将他们逼到角落
But if we push them into a corner,
他们就会现出原形了
they will act like common criminals.
事情会变得很难看
And it will get ugly.
这就是我们的工作 孩子
Ugly is what we do, son.
-长官 -什么事
- Sir? - Yes?
我觉得你得看看这个
I think you should see this.
随时会出现在镜头里
Coming through frame any second...
-那里 -是他们
- There! - That's them.
博迪会完成尾崎的使命 不惜代价
Bodhi's gonna finish what Ozaki started, no matter what.
但他需要钱来铺路
But he needs money to do that.
我们把他们的资产冻结了 他们什么也干不成
We've frozen their assets. They can't do a damn thing.
休 那片区域有多少家银行
Hugh, how many banks are in the area?
有十好几家
There's more than a dozen.
但今天是星期六 没有一家开门
But this is Saturday, none are open.
除了山顶上的一家小支行
Except a small branch on top of the mountain.
但没人会疯到去打它的主意的
But no one would be crazy enough to try anything there.
这群人就会
These guys would be.
它在山顶上
It's on top of a mountain.
上下山只有一条路 那里是交通阻塞点
Only one road, up or down. A total chokepoint.
阻塞点正合了他们的意
Chokepoint is exactly what they want.
向当地警局示警
Alert local law enforcement.
该是时候决定你的立场了
It's time to choose whose side you're on.
我并不想正式警告你
I'm not officially doin' this.
但我不希望你在我的照看下死掉 所以千万别死
I don't want you dyin' on my watch, so don't.
博迪
Bodhi!
-不要 -别开枪
- No! - Hold your fire!
别开枪
Hold your fire!
啊
Ah!
快走
Move!
拦住他
Cut 'im off!
博迪
Bodhi!
博迪 不 不要
Bodhi, no! No!
那是一个计划清单
That's one hell of a bucket list.
尾崎八项
1.力之涌动 2.天之降诞 3.地之觉醒 4.水之生灵
5.风之永动 6.冰之固结 7.命之主宰 8.终极幸运
第四条为什么没有划掉
Why isn't number four crossed off?
我还以为他已经冲过浪了
I thought he surfed the wave.
他选择了救我
He chose to save my life instead.
是吗
Yeah.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
嗯
Yeah.
没人说过这项工作会很轻松
Nobody said it was gonna be an easy job.
噢 天啊
Oh, God.
我知道他要去哪儿了
I know where he's goin'.
前面六次考验都向着同一个方向行进 向下
The first six ordeals all travel in one direction, down.
利用重力
With gravity.
但是第七次考验 命之主宰
But Seven, "Master of Six Lives,"
要求反重力而行 往上
Asks you to go against gravity, go up.
单人自由攀岩
Free solo rock climbing.
没有绳索 没有保护措施 没有第二次机会
And no ropes, no protection, no second chances.
全世界只有少数几个攀岩之处
Now, there are just a handful of ascents in the world
符合尾崎对于挑战的要求
that match Ozaki's standard for the impossible,
而且只有一处位于
but only one that lies
美国政府无从下手的地方
outside of the reach of the U.S. Government.
安赫尔瀑布 位于委内瑞拉
Angel Falls, Venezuela.
那也是博迪出生的国家
It's also the country that Bodhi was born in.
你很聪明
Very smart.
打扰了 长官 有你的电话
Excuse me, sir. There is a call for you.
我会给他打回去的
I'll call him back.
我们同委内瑞拉没有外交关系
We have no diplomatic relationships with Venezuela.
也没有同他们签署引渡条约
We have no extradition treaty with Venezuela.
等这混蛋下次冒出来时 我们再抓他
We get this son-of-a-bitch when he pops up next.
那么 听着
So, look,
如果他在这次考验中活了下来 他就还剩两次考验了 对吗
if he survives this next ordeal, he's got two left, correct?
是的 长官
That's right, sir.
但是像法国海岸那样的海浪非常罕见
But the wave like the one off France is incredibly rare.
下次再有那种规模的海浪可能是几年以后了
It could be years until there's a swell that size again.
并且第八次考验 终极信任 是个谜
And the 8th Ordeal, "Act of Ultimate Trust," Is a mystery.
没人知道那是什么意思
No one knows what it means.
我得在博迪接受
I need to get to Bodhi
第七次考验开始行动之前找到他
in the 7th Ordeal before he starts to climb.
否则就再也找不到他了
Otherwise he is gone.
我们根本没法进入那个国家
We can't even get into the country.
我会把握住这次机会的 长官
I will not let this go, sir.
你还不明白吗 我们拿他没办法
Do you understand? He's out of reach.
我犯了错误 现在 我明白了
I make mistakes. Now, I know that.
但我向你保证 我能完成这项任务
But I promised you I could do this job.
我得结束这一切
I need to finish it.
帕
Pap,
我们能把他送过去吗
can we get him in?
嗯 可以
Yeah, it could be done.
-嘿 就是这儿吗 -是的
- Hey. This it? - Si.
千万要保住性命 孩子
Try not to get yourself killed, kid.
博迪 我看不见路了
Bodhi, I can't see the line.
什么也没有
Nothing.
我看见了
I do.
我看见了 很漂亮
I do see it, and it's beautiful.
你知道我一直相信你 对吧
You know I always trusted you, right?
但是循着一条我压根看不见的路
To follow a line I can't even see?
那不是我的线路 是你的
It's not my line. It's yours.
博迪
Bodhi!
结束了
It's over!
见鬼
Shit!
来吧
Come on!
你可以做到的 上来
You can get it! Go for it!
你能做到的
You can do it.
嘿 格罗美特 来啊
Hey, Grommet, come on.
坚持一下马上就到了
回见
See you soon.
你无处可逃了
You've got nowhere to go!
你知道你违反了多少条法律吗
Do you have any idea how many laws you've broken?
你杀了多少人
How many people you killed?
而你一无所成
And you accomplished nothing.
也许吧
Maybe.
但我还没完成
But I'm not done yet.
博迪 不
Bodhi! No!
不要
No!
没有衣服 没有鞋子 没有尸体 什么也没有
No gear, no shoes, no body, nothin'.
很可能已经飘到下游好几英里的地方去了
Probably miles downriver by now.
可能永远也找不到尸体了
Might never find the body.
终极信任
The Act of Ultimate Trust
博迪是故意从瀑布顶上跳下来的
Bodhi went over the falls on purpose.
第八次考验
The 8th Ordeal.
他弄懂了
He figured it out.
加急赶出来的
Had it fast-tracked.
联邦调查局
科特斯海丘 太平洋
十七个月后
世界真小 不是吗
I guess this is really a small world, isn't it?
我就知道只要你还活着
I just knew if you were alive anywhere on the Earth,
你就不可能放手
there's no way you'd let this go.
水之生灵
"Life of Water."
只剩这一个你就能完成全部八次考验了
It's the last ordeal you need to complete The Eight.
你为什么在这儿 犹他
Why are you here, Utah?
海浪有一百英尺高 起码
It's 100-foot out there. More.
你没穿救生衣
You got no PFD.
你离海岸一百五十英里 我来这儿是要把你带回去
You're 150 miles from shore. I'm here to take you in,
因为一旦你过去了 就再也回不来了 博迪
because if you go out there, you're not comin' back, Bodhi!
那不是很美吗
And isn't that beautiful?
那难道不美吗
Isn't that beautiful?
那不美吗 兄弟
Isn't that beautiful, brother?
这是我的路
This is my path.
让我完成它
Let me complete it.
回见 犹他
See you soon, Utah.
去哪儿
Where to?
回家
Home.
--=梦幻天堂·龙网=--
http://www.321n.net